Let go of my daughter.
اترك ابنتي
You really are meeting in secret here.
أنتم حقا تجتمعون سرا هنا.
Outrageous!
صادم!
Step aside.
تنحى.
If I kill him now,
إذا قتلته الآن،
no one will ever know about this.
لن يعرف أحد هذا أبدًا.
Father, please don't kill him.
أبي من فضلك لا تقتله.
Boy,
ولد،
let me ask you.
دعني اسألك.
What is your name?
ما اسمك؟
Who is your master?
من هو سيدك؟
State your name and lineage at once.
اذكر اسمك ونسبك مرة واحدة.
Uncle Jiang,
العم جيانغ
my name is Chen Yuanqi.
اسمي تشين يوانكي.
I am twenty years old.
عمري عشرين سنة.
I was a villager from Feiyun Village.
كنت قرويًا من قرية فييون.
I was still studying before.
كنت لا أزال أدرس من قبل.
I am just a sword slave.
أنا مجرد عبد السيف.
I'll kill you!
سأقتلك!
Father!
أب!
No!
لا!
Yumeng!
يومينج!
As the legitimate daughter of the Jiang family,
باعتبارها الابنة الشرعية لعائلة جيانغ،
you secretly meet with a mere commoner here.
تلتقي سراً مع شخص عادي هنا.
Do you realize
هل تدرك
the Jiang family is lacking talented heirs now?
هل تفتقر عائلة جيانج إلى الورثة الموهوبين الآن؟
I have no son.
ليس لدي ابن.
I can only hope for you
لا أستطيع إلا أن أتمنى لك
to bring me a noble clan son-in-law through marriage alliance.
أن أحضر لي صهرًا من عشيرة نبيلة من خلال تحالف الزواج.
Only then will we not be outdone by other noble clans.
حينها فقط لن نكون متفوقين على العشائر النبيلة الأخرى.
But you—
ولكنك-
Are you trying to drive me mad?
هل تحاول أن تجعلني مجنونا؟
Father,
أب،
Yuanqi and I truly love each other.
أنا ويوانكي نحب بعضنا البعض حقًا.
How much is true love worth?
كم يساوي الحب الحقيقي؟
For the Jiang family's honor and your reputation,
من أجل شرف عائلة جيانغ وسمعتك،
I must kill him today.
يجب أن أقتله اليوم.
Yuanqi!
يوانكي!
Boy,
ولد،
were you wounded by Du Gu Zhantian's Demon Subduing Art?
هل أصيبت بجروح بسبب فن إخضاع الشياطين الخاص بـ Du Gu Zhantian؟
Yes.
نعم.
Father,
أب،
the Fu family killed for treasure out of ambition.
عائلة فو قتلت من أجل الكنز بدافع الطموح.
They secretly revived Du Gu Zhantian.
قاموا بإحياء دو جو زانتيان سراً.
Yuanqi fought and was gravely injured.
لقد قاتل يوانكي وأصيب بجروح خطيرة.
That's how we managed to survive.
وهكذا تمكنا من البقاء على قيد الحياة.
Du Gu Zhantian has been revived?
هل تم إحياء Du Gu Zhantian؟
Boy,
ولد،
what martial art do you practice?
ما هو الفن القتالي الذي تمارسه؟
Heaven-defying Immortal Technique.
تقنية الخالد التي تتحدى السماء.
It's not a noble clan technique.
إنها ليست تقنية عشيرة نبيلة.
No matter how powerful it is,
بغض النظر عن مدى قوتها،
you have no backing.
ليس لديك أي دعم.
You come from a poor background.
أنت تأتي من خلفية فقيرة.
My Jiang family is a century-old noble clan.
عائلتي جيانج هي عشيرة نبيلة عمرها قرن من الزمان.
How could we accept
كيف يمكننا أن نقبل
someone of low status and weak foundation as a son-in-law?
شخص ذو مكانة منخفضة وأساس ضعيف كصهر؟
Father,
أب،
if Yuanqi dies today,
إذا مات يوانكي اليوم،
I won't live either.
أنا أيضا لن أعيش.
You—
أنت-
Yumeng!
يومينج!
Please spare him, Father. Yumeng!
أرجوك أن تنقذه يا أبي. يومينغ!
Fine.
بخير.
Boy,
ولد،
I'll give you one chance.
سأعطيك فرصة واحدة.
Within one year,
خلال سنة واحدة،
Yumeng must enter a marriage alliance.
يجب على Yumeng الدخول في تحالف زواج.
If you become a universally acknowledged top expert,
إذا أصبحت خبيرًا بارزًا معترفًا به عالميًا،
then you may come to the Jiang family for me.
ثم يمكنك أن تأتي إلى عائلة جيانج من أجلي.
What marriage alliance?
ما هو تحالف الزواج؟
Why didn't I know about this?
لماذا لم أعلم بهذا؟
It's a family arrangement.
إنه ترتيب عائلي.
You have no choice.
ليس لديك خيار.
Uncle Jiang,
العم جيانغ
within one year,
خلال سنة واحدة،
I will come to Guanghan Jiang family.
سوف آتي إلى عائلة قوانغهان جيانج.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Yuanqi!
يوانكي!
Yumeng! Yuanqi!
يومينج! يوانكي!
Yumeng!
يومينج!
Yuanqi!
يوانكي!
Boy,
ولد،
I'll wait for you in Shangjing.
سأنتظرك في شانغجينج.
It hurts so much...
إنه يؤلمني كثيرا...
I'm still alive.
أنا لا أزال على قيد الحياة.
Saintess,
قديسة،
what should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Why did I hold on until her father left?
لماذا بقيت متمسكة بها حتى رحل والدها؟
I can lose.
أستطيع أن أخسر.
I can even die.
حتى أنني أستطيع أن أموت.
But I don't want to be looked down on.
لكنني لا أريد أن ينظر إلي بازدراء.
Especially by the woman I care about.
وخاصة من قبل المرأة التي أهتم بها.
I rather admire your shameless persistence.
أنا معجب بإصرارك الوقح.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Why did you hit me?
لماذا ضربتني؟
Kid.
طفل.
I've cleared your ear channels.
لقد قمت بتنظيف قنوات أذنك.
Listen to the west and see what secrets you find.
استمع إلى الغرب وانظر ما هي الأسرار التي ستجدها.
Deep within the Forest of the Beast God,
في أعماق غابة إله الوحش،
could there still be a divine weapon hidden?
هل لا يزال من الممكن أن يكون هناك سلاح إلهي مخفي؟
This place is near Banquan.
هذا المكان بالقرب من بانكوان.
A thousand years ago,
منذ ألف سنة،
the human and immortal realms, together with the Beast God clan,
العوالم البشرية والخالدة، إلى جانب عشيرة إله الوحش،
fought a legendary battle here.
خاض معركة أسطورية هنا.
I sense a peerless divine weapon lying dormant here.
أشعر بوجود سلاح إلهي لا مثيل له كامن هنا.
It is about to awaken.
إنه على وشك الاستيقاظ.
What?
ماذا؟
There's a teahouse here?
هل يوجد بيت شاي هنا؟
That's unusual.
هذا أمر غير عادي.
Perfect.
ممتاز.
Let's find a place to rest.
دعونا نجد مكانا للراحة.
And gather some information while we're at it.
وجمع بعض المعلومات أثناء قيامنا بذلك.
Is anyone here?
هل يوجد أحد هنا؟
Boss.
رئيس.
Honored guest.
ضيف شرف.
What would you like to drink?
ماذا تحب أن تشرب؟
Just some plain tea.
فقط بعض الشاي العادي.
You have good taste.
لديك ذوق جيد.
Our tea is the finest in the area.
الشاي لدينا هو الأفضل في المنطقة.
Thank you for your trouble.
شكرا على تعبك.
Madam.
سيدتي.
Madam, please come here.
سيدتي، من فضلك تعالي إلى هنا.
What would you like to drink, sir?
ماذا تريد أن تشرب يا سيدي؟
Bring your best wine and food
أحضر أفضل أنواع النبيذ والطعام
and serve them all to me.
وأخدمهم جميعا لي.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
We're giving you business,
نحن نقدم لك الأعمال،
can't even touch you a little?
لا أستطيع أن ألمسك حتى قليلا؟
Come here!
تعال الى هنا!
Stop!
قف!
Kid.
طفل.
While I'm in a good mood,
بينما أنا في مزاج جيد،
you better get lost.
من الأفضل أن تضيع.
Or else...
وإلا...
Don't blame me for showing no mercy.
لا تلوموني على عدم إظهار الرحمة.
So, you poor brat,
إذن، أيها المسكين،
you dare meddle in the affairs of the Demon Sect?
هل تجرؤ على التدخل في شؤون طائفة الشياطين؟
Do you even know who you are?
هل تعرف من أنت حقًا؟
Go.
يذهب.
Hold her down for me.
امسكها من أجلي.
Come here, little demon.
تعال هنا، أيها الشيطان الصغير.
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Thank you, sir, for saving my life.
شكرا لك سيدي على إنقاذ حياتي.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
Madam.
سيدتي.
Running a teahouse deep in the forest,
إدارة بيت شاي في أعماق الغابة،
why are you alone here?
لماذا أنت وحدك هنا؟
I am from the demon clan.
انا من عشيرة الشياطين.
I run this teahouse in the Forest of the Beast God to make a living.
أدير هذا المقهى في غابة إله الوحش لكسب لقمة العيش.
I didn't expect
لم اتوقع
to only catch a few Demon Sect lackeys.
للقبض فقط على عدد قليل من أتباع طائفة الشياطين.
But I caught a big one.
لكنني اصطدت واحدة كبيرة.
You woke up even after being poisoned by me.
لقد استيقظت حتى بعد أن تسممت من قبلي.
Your cultivation is impressive.
زراعتك مثيرة للإعجاب.
Are you with the Demon Sect?
هل أنت مع طائفة الشيطان؟
The Demon Sect's methods are still so despicable.
لا تزال أساليب طائفة الشياطين حقيرة للغاية.
Bah!
باه!
I am Qingluo, servant to Lie Shumei, the Beast God clan's saintess.
أنا تشينغلو، خادمة لي شومي، قديسة عشيرة إله الوحش.
I serve her as a maid.
أنا أخدمها كخادمة.
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
Du Gu Zhantian coveted the Beast God clan.
كان دو جو زانتيان يطمع في عشيرة إله الوحش.
The saintess feigned compliance,
تظاهرت القديسة بالامتثال،
endured humiliation and became the Demon Sect's saintess,
تحملت الإذلال وأصبحت قديسة طائفة الشياطين،
just to protect our clan.
فقط لحماية عشيرتنا.
I killed those Demon Sect members just now,
لقد قتلت أعضاء طائفة الشيطان للتو،
so I saved you too.
لذلك أنقذتك أيضًا.
Why did you still try to harm me?
لماذا مازلت تحاول أن تؤذيني؟
Because the technique Du Gu Zhantian taught the saintess is flawed.
لأن التقنية التي علمها دو جو زانتيان للقديسة معيبة.
Every ten years,
كل عشر سنوات،
the saintess loses her strength.
القديسة تفقد قوتها
I must find suitable cultivators
يجب أن أجد المزارعين المناسبين
and seize their cultivation pills
والاستيلاء على حبوب زراعتهم
for the saintess to absorb and restore her power.
لكي تتمكن القديسة من امتصاص قوتها واستعادتها.
Sir,
سيد،
forgive my offense.
اغفر لي خطيئتي.
I will repay you in my next life.
سأكافئك في حياتي القادمة.
Please don't kill me.
من فضلك لا تقتلني.
Don't kill me!
لا تقتلني!
When you tried to kill me just now,
عندما حاولت قتلي للتو،
you didn't hesitate at all.
لم تتردد على الإطلاق.
Spare me, sir!
انقذني يا سيدي!
My family is in Lie Shumei's hands.
عائلتي في يد لي شومي.
I have no choice but to obey.
ليس لدي خيار سوى الطاعة.
If you let me go,
إذا سمحت لي بالذهاب،
I can lead you to the treasure.
أستطيع أن أقودك إلى الكنز.
There is a divine weapon here.
هناك سلاح إلهي هنا.
How do I know you're not lying?
كيف أعرف أنك لا تكذب؟
If you don't believe me,
إذا كنت لا تصدقني،
I can swear an oath.
أستطيع أن أقسم اليمين.
If I speak even half a lie,
إذا تكلمت حتى نصف كذبة،
may I never die a good death.
لا أتمنى أن أموت موتة طيبة أبدًا.
and forever be your servant.
وأكون خادمك إلى الأبد.
Then tell me,
ثم أخبرني
what kind of divine weapon is it?
ما هو نوع السلاح الإلهي هذا؟
It's the sacred treasure of the Beast God Clan.
إنه الكنز المقدس لعشيرة إله الوحش.
Chi You’s Divine Sword.
سيف تشي يو الإلهي.
Legend says it was the sword of the ancient war god Chi You.
تقول الأسطورة أن هذا كان سيف إله الحرب القديم تشي يو.
It holds boundless divine power.
فهو يحمل قوة إلهية لا حدود لها.
If you obtain it,
إذا حصلت عليه،
you will surely stand above all others.
سوف تقف بالتأكيد فوق كل الآخرين.
I'm warning you,
انا احذرك
if you dare deceive me again,
إذا تجرأت على خداعي مرة أخرى،
next time,
المرة التالية،
I won’t show any mercy.
لن أظهر أي رحمة.
I won’t.
أنا لن.
Lead the way.
قيادة الطريق.
It’s just ahead.
إنه فقط للأمام.
This is Chi You’s Divine Sword.
هذا هو سيف تشي يو الإلهي.
Yes.
نعم.
Chi You’s Divine Sword.
سيف تشي يو الإلهي.
The divine sword is here.
السيف الإلهي هنا.
Now we’re even.
الآن نحن متعادلون.
You may leave.
يمكنك المغادرة.
I’m still useful to you, sir.
لا أزال مفيداً لك يا سيدي.
I can teach you how to draw the sword.
أستطيع أن أعلمك كيفية رسم السيف.
The sword is already here.
السيف موجود بالفعل هنا.
Why would I need your help?
لماذا أحتاج إلى مساعدتك؟
That’s not it.
هذا ليس هو.
Without the right method, you can’t draw it.
بدون الطريقة الصحيحة، لا يمكنك رسمه.
Try it if you don’t believe me.
جربه إذا كنت لا تصدقني.